(车臣)
说
Talk.
快说
最后通牒
For the last time,
从巴黎监狱释放阿卜杜勒·萨尔曼·阿尔-阿尔坎
release Abdel Salman al-Arkan from his prison in Paris.
我是卢卡斯·格雷夫斯 IDP报社 声明完毕
This is Lucas Graves, IDP News, signing off.
求求你们 他们会杀了我们所有人
Please. They're gonna kill us all!
放了他 不然45分钟后直播行刑
Release him, or the execution plays live in 45 minutes.
他们会杀了我们
They're gonna kill us.
坚强点
Stay strong.
目标确认
Destination confirmed.
你应该杀了他们
You should kill them.
作出强势声明 西方人杀了自己人
A powerful statement, a Westerner killing his own people.
重新计算路径
Recalculating route.
他们早该打电话了
They should have called.
他们应该早打电话了
They should have called already!
不 不 不 求你了
No. No. No, please!
求你别杀我
Please don't kill me!
走 快走
Go. Go!
快点 快走 走
Come on. Move. Go!
他们要逃走了 快追 快追
They're getting away! Let's go! Let's go!
快
Go.
我去检查北边
I'll take the north side.
好
OK!
继续搜索南边
Keep searching the south side
封锁周围
Lock down the perimeter.
妈的 他不在这儿
Shit. He's not here.
快让他们上车
Get them on the truck now.
快走 快走
Let's go! Let's go!
金布拉还没到 他拿着钥匙
Kimbral's not here. He's got the keys.
快啊
Come on!
那是什么鬼东西？
What the fuck was that?
我们该走了 树
We got to go, Shu.
快啊 快啊 快
Come on, come on, come on.
金布拉究竟在哪？
Where the hell's Kimbral?
你迟到了40秒 金布拉
You are 40 seconds late, Kimbral.
走 快
Go, go!
你究竟跑哪儿去了？
Where the hell were you?
- 她中枪了 - 让开地方 让开
- She's been shot. - Give me room. Give me room!
爱丽丝 爱丽丝
Alice. Alice!
快醒啊
Come on.
该死
Damn it.
艾比
Abby!
让开 让开 让开 怎么啦？
Move, move, move, move, move. What happened?
她胸口中枪
She's shot in the chest.
到底怎么回事用这么长时间？
What the hell took you guys so long?
该死 妈的
Shit. Fuck.
好啦
Okay.
噢 上帝
Oh, God.
她死了
She's gone.
妈的
Shit.
这都怪你
This is on you.
到底出了什么事？
What the hell happened?
该死
Goddamn it.
出了什么事？
What happened?
我有机会炸了他们的武器库 我就去炸了
I had a chance to blow their weapons load, and I took it.
- 他妈的计划里没有这个内容 - 我自己加的
- It wasn't part of the fucking plan! - I factored it in.
- 你自己加的？- 我的路线 速度…
- Oh, you factored it in? - The route I took, the speed...
- 你刚才在哪儿？- 你是不是用了你的计算机程序？
- Where were you? - Did you use your computer program?
树 根本没有可能…
Shu, there was less than point zero zero...
树 算法非常可靠
Shu, the algorithm was solid.
你损失了一名人质？
You lost a hostage?
老板要生气了
Bossman's gonna be pissed.
快他妈带我们离开这儿 哈什
Get us the fuck out of here, Hush.
(佐治亚州 亚特兰大)
- 你要见我？- 是的 进来坐下吧
- You wanted to see me? - Yeah. Come on in and sit down.
我要让你走人
I'm letting you go.
- 什么？- 我要让你走人
- What? - l'm letting you go.
我不再需要你执行任务
I won't be needing your services anymore.
你知道 这项工作中最重要的要求
You know, the most important thing in this job
是知道你能够相信身边的人
is knowing you can trust the guy next to you.
我以前告诉过你 你的这个程序还未就绪
I told you before. This program of yours, it wasn't ready,
而且你藐视团队
and you defied the team.
是我的程序未就绪 还是你根本就不喜欢？
My program's not ready, or you just don't like it?
死了一个人质
A woman died.
不用这个算法也可能会死人 别都怪在我头上
Could've happened without the algorithm. Don't you put that on me.
你的脑子就在想找些借口"算法"
You want to make all these excuses up in your head: algorithm.
不管什么原因 有人死了
Whatever it is, someone died
因为你相信计算机而不是你的团队
because you trusted a computer more than your own team.
你可以走了
You got to go.
跟你说过我们扩张太快了
Told you we expanded too fast.
你是打算坐在那训我还是回去工作？
You gonna sit there and bust my balls or get back to work?
下次我会听你的… 也许
Next time, I'll listen to you... maybe.
怎么说 "我太蠢了"？
How do you say, quote, "I am stupid"?
真是太彪了
I'm stupid.
你为什么想学青岛话？
Why do you want to learn Qingdao?
西方人是几乎不可能听懂的
It's almost impossible for a Westernear to decipher.
我喜欢不可能
I like the impossible.
这个游戏 围棋 很有趣
This game, Go, is interesting.
你觉得为什么总是你赢？
Why do you think you win all the time?
因为我从四岁开始就下围棋了
Because I've been playing Go since I was four,
而你两年前才开始学
and you started two years ago.
每一步棋都相互联系
You move everything together.
每一领地都属于一个整体
You take the territory as one.
你吃掉我整块的棋子 所有的一切都当成一个整体
You take my pieces as one. Everything flows as one.
而你们在处理绑架案的时候 没人做到整体配合行动
When you were at the factory, none of your guys moved together.
你们没有形成一个整体
You didn't flow as one.
金布拉想要抢你的风头
Kimbral was trying to upstage you.
也许我该单枪匹马
Maybe I should work alone.
没有人能单枪匹马做事情
No one does it alone.
我想我在执行任务的时候 脑子里听到的就是你这个声音
I guess that's why I hear your voice in my head when I am on the job.
可能听起来像我 但我认为那声音是你的直觉
It may sound like me, but I think that voice is your intuition.
你好好考虑考虑
Take all the time you need,
但等你回来的时候 我希望你具备团队精神
but when you come back, I need you to be a team player.
别像金布拉那样
Don't be like Kimbral.
别混淆直觉和自负
Don't confuse intuition with ego.
相信我 树 永远倾听你的直觉
Trust me on this one, Shu. Always listen to your intuition.
永远
Always.
(一年后)
(中国 上海)
最初的通信卫星
The original communication satellite
只能解决一个问题…
set out to solve one problem...
就是如何将信号成功地经过弯曲的地球球面
how to send a signal successfully around the bend in the Earth
传递给接收方
and reach the receiver.
今天 我们雨声技术公司很荣幸地为您呈现
Today, we at Yusheng Technology are proud to present to you
卫星技术的未来
the future of satellite tech.
我们速度更快 体积更小…
We do it faster, with smaller units...
这就是投影会发生变化的地方？
Now this is where the graphics are gonna change?
我已经说过我不需要投影了
I don't need graphics!
这不是太阳马戏团
This isn't Cirque de Soleil.
我说到卫星的时候 你要让老虎跳出来吗？
Maybe a tiger can jump out when I get to the cubesats.
秦
Chin!
你可以帮我解释吗
A little help here please.
怎么啦？我喜欢老虎
What? I like tigers.
好啦 大家听着 我们重新设置 五分钟后再来一遍
Okay, everyone, let's reset and go again in five.
- 雨声？- 嗯？
- Yusheng? - Huh?
别担心 小兄弟 你是最棒的
Don't worry, little bro. You'll be great.
谢谢
Thank you.
没想到在这里见到你
I didn't expect to see you here.
你的工作比我忙
Your job keeps you busier than I am.
没想到当一个安全专家很花时间
Who knew being a security specialist was so time-consuming?
下周我要去澳门出差
I have a job next week in Macao.
真好 那我们离得近了
So you were in the neighborhood.
很高兴见到你 秦
It's great to see you, Chin.
希望我对你弟弟也能这样打招呼
I wish I could say the same thing about your brother.
我能帮你做什么？
What can I help you with?
雨声有麻烦了
Yusheng is in trouble.
不管是不是天才 他都满不在乎
Genius or not, he's careless.
- 很多人想让他死 - 谁？
- Lot of people want to see him die. - Who?
我最担心的是一家叫拉什科的公司
A company called Ruscho is who I'm most worried about.
他们是家科技巨头 总部位于日内瓦
They're a tech giant headquartered in Geneva,
他们已经三次提出控股收购雨声 他都拒绝了
and they tried to buy Yusheng out three times already, and he's refused.
这些家伙可不是甘心被拒绝的人
These are not the kind of guys who take no for an answer.
他这个周末要去曼谷参加单身派对
He's going to Bangkok this weekend for a bachelor party,
所以他不愿带保镖
and he won't take a bodyguard.
我给你付钱
I'll pay you.
我们是一家人 没必要这样
We are family. Not necessary.
(泰国 曼谷)
好的 表弟 我送你回家
Party's over. Let's go.
大哥 陪我再玩一会
I'm glad you're here.
这个地方不安全
It's not safe here.
走啦 表弟
I'm taking you home.
我是"伽利略" 你是囚犯1764号
I am Galileo. You are inmate 1764.
重复 你是囚犯1764号
I repeat, you are inmate 1764.
欢迎来到哈迪斯
Welcome to Hades.
囚犯1764号请注意
Attention, inmate 1764.
你被指派参加竞技区搏斗
You have been reported to battle in the zoo.
搏斗开始
Begin battle.
搏斗结束
The battle is over.
囚犯1764号
Inmate 1764,
你赢得两小时的庇护时光
you have earned two hours of sanctuary time.
其他囚犯请返回各自囚室
All remaining inmates return to your spoke.
你还好吗？
You Okay?
所有囚犯请返回各自囚室
All prisoners return to your spoke.
我们肯定能找到可以说话的人…
There must be someone we could talk to...
把我们带出去 我没做错什么
to get us out of here. I didn't do anything wrong.
我没做错什么
I didn't do anything wrong.
囚犯1764号 去安全屋报到
Inmate 1764, report to the sanctuary.
这是什么？
What is this?
应该是赢家要去的地方
Must be where the winners go.
树失踪了 法律上的失踪 你那里有什么消息？
Shu's gone. This is legit. What do you got?
他表姐说她找他们十八小时了 运气不佳
His cousin says she's been trying them both for 18 hours. No luck.
- 派对是周六晚上 - 从派对上有没有收获？
- Party happened Saturday night. - What'd you get from the party?
没有安保录像 什么都没有
No security tapes, nothing.
好吧 我来跟进
All right, I'll look into it.
所有囚犯返回各自囚室
All prisoners return to your spoke.
在监狱里 他们首先要做的就是摧毁你的精神
The first thing they try to do in lockup is break your spirit.
绝不允许发生那样的事 你必须在心理上保持强大
Can't allow that to happen. You have to stay mentally strong.
成功越狱需要关注三个关键因素
You have to focus on three key things to a successful breakout.
哪三个？
What are they?
一 了解布局结构
One, know the layout.
二 熟悉日常规律
Two, understand the routine.
三 有内部或外部的支援
Three, have help from the inside or out.
准确来说就是团队合作 你的最爱 我可以断定
Teamwork. Exactly. Your favorite one, I can tell.
千万记住 树 团队行动 所有的一切都是一个整体
Remember, Shu, you move together. Everything flows as one.
一七六四
One, seven, six, four.
你是监狱长？
Are you the warden?
你表弟很有才气
Your cousin is a brilliant man.
他给我说了他专利的细节 34ACJL号专利
He gave me the details of his patent, number 34ACJL.
但没有说36BBBCK号专利
But not number 36BBBCK.
我需要你去说服他把专利卖给我
I need you to convince him to give that to me.
我为什么要那样做？
Why would I do that?
你们一起长大
You grew up together.
像亲兄弟一样
Like brothers.
但你们不是亲兄弟
But you weren't brothers.
一场家庭悲剧让你不得不和他一起生活
A family tragedy forced you to live with him.
你恨雨声
You hated Yusheng.
他为什么总是比别人聪明
How he was always smarter than everyone else.
他本可以帮助很多人 可他只顾自己
He could've helped a lot of people, but he went for himself instead,
他有钱了
and he got rich.
现在 他对金钱的迷恋…
And now, his love of money...
他的宝贵专利…
his precious patent...
会让你送命
is going to get you killed.
我对我的囚犯了如指掌
I know everything about my animals.
想知道我是谁？
You want to know who I am?
我是动物园管理员
I'm the Zookeeper.
所有囚犯在竞技区报到
All prisoners report to the zoo.
- 所有囚犯在竞技区报到 - 你跟他说了什么？
- All prisoners report to the zoo. - What did you tell him?
什么？
What?
你交出了第一个专利
You gave up the first patent.
那又怎样？他们折磨我 那个专利不重要
So? They were torturing me. That one's nothing.
- 他清楚我们的背景 - 我没告诉他
- He knew things about our background. - I didn't tell him.
第二个专利 是什么？
The second patent, what is it?
高级立方星技术 游戏规则颠覆者
Advanced cube satellite tech. It's a game changer.
它能越权控制全球任何一台计算机系统
It can override and control any computer system in the world.
就像一把网络万能钥匙 但也不是你想象的那样
Like a cyber skeleton key. And it's not what you think.
这无关金钱 我申请了专利就为的是埋葬它
This isn't about money. I patented it so I could bury it.
落到了坏人的手里 游戏就结束了
In the wrong hands, game over.
防御系统 核弹程式 没人能够置身事外
Defense systems, nuclear codes. No one will be safe.
金布拉
Kimbral.
不 不
No, no.
并不是每天都要搏斗
Not every day is a fight day.
我们在这干什么？
What are we doing here?
我是他表弟
I'm his cousin.
我们俩出现在这里绝对不是巧合
I don't think it's a coincidence that we both are here.
我想他们是在寻找布雷斯林
I think they're after Breslin.
你们知道 干了这么长时间
You know, after spending a lot of time with this,
我把耳朵贴在地面上
I put my ear to the ground,
我不喜欢我看到的 我不喜欢我听到的
I just didn't like what I saw, didn't like what I heard.
你到这多久了？
How long have you been here?
很难说
It's hard to say.
我猜… 大概有几个月了
My best guess is... couple of months.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
有很多谣传 跟神话一样
There's a lot of rumors, like mythology.
这个叫高价值资产监禁服务
It's called the High Asset Detention Service.
哈迪斯
Hades.
希腊神话？
Greek mythology?
冥王府
Land of the dead.
不管是谁都有进无出 就这么简单
Whoever goes in just doesn't come out. It's that simple.
- 听起来很熟悉 - 是啊
- Sounds familiar. - Yeah.
据说"坟墓"背后的人会遭受毒打 经过调整
The word is the people behind the Tomb took a beating, did some adjustments,
- 回来会更强大 - 这些可恶的家伙都是什么人？
-and then came back strong. - Who are these assholes?
间谍 罪犯 商人 官员
Spies, criminals, businessmen, elected officials.
利益 巨大利益
Profit. Big profit.
你怎么会认为他在那儿？
What makes you think he's there?
他的表弟雨声被列在了竞争对手的暗杀名单上
His cousin Yusheng was put on some kind of hit list by his competition,
一家叫拉什科的卫星技术公司
a satellite tech company called Ruscho.
有搏斗日 也有休战日
There's battle days and there's truce days.
如果你能赢得搏斗 你就有福利
If you win a battle, you get benefits.
如果你搏斗失败 或拒绝搏斗…
If you lose or refuse to fight...
你在这里的日子就不会好过
your time in here is very uncomfortable.
这就是他们把这里叫"动物园"的原因 我们都是园里的动物
That's why they call it "the zoo." We're all animals here.
适者生存
Survival of the fittest.
如果他们特别想让某人消失 为什么不直接杀了他？
If you want someone to disappear so bad, why not just kill them?
如果那样 全世界都会知道他们死了
Because then the world will know they are dead.
在这儿 他们只是消失
Here, they are just gone.
那我们应该进去救他们出来
Then we got to go in, get them out.
不能盲目进入 我们不了解布局结构
Can't go in there blind. We don't know a layout.
- 我们什么都不了解 - 你一无所知时也曾闯过"坟墓"
- We don't have anything. - You broke the Tomb totally blind.
是的 不过 那是我运气好
Yeah, well, I got lucky.
我们甚至都不肯定树是否就在那里
We don't even know for sure if Shu's there.
- 如果他在那儿呢？- 听着 如果他在那里 我们会救他出来
- And what if he is? - Look, if he's there, we'll get him.
如果盲目进去 我们自己也会被困
We go in there blind, we get trapped ourselves.
你觉得我处理不了
You don't think I can handle it.
它比我们任何一个人都强大
This is bigger than any one of us.
好吧
All right.
先生 出现数据外泄 有人侵入我们的系统
Sir, we've got a data breach. Someone's in our system.
什么？
What?
关闭系统 马上关闭系统
Shut it down. Shut it down now.
在为晚上扫清障碍
Just cleaning up for the night.
这是我在拉什科的唯一联络人
Here's the only contact I got at Ruscho.
不知道他会不会跟你说话 但总归是个不错的切入点
Not sure if he'll talk to you, but it's a good place to start.
就一张便利贴？
A sticky note?
- 你有什么消息？- 好的
- So what do you got? - All right.
两样东西 一个神秘的银行帐户 代码麻雀
Two things. A dark bank account, code-named Sparrow,
拉什科持续给这个帐户汇款
Ruscho's been sending money to.
他们给利昂·格拉西汇了一千万
And they also sent ten million to Leon Grassi,
私营监狱产业的说客
a lobbyist for the private prison industry.
我知道这个利昂·格拉西
I know this Leon Grassi.
他曾为监狱局工作了十三年
He used to work for the prison board for about 13 years,
每次我从他的地盘脱逃出来
and then he started taking a lot of heat
他会受到很多批评
every time I broke out of one of his places,
因此他决定跳槽到私人监狱
so he decided to jump into the private sector.
自那以后再没他的消息
Haven't heard from him since.
今天你看上去很漂亮 其实你自己知道的
You look very nice today, but you know that.
给你拿杯喝的？
Get you a drink?
不喝你这里卖的
Not what you got, Tiny.
我知道你不会就这样改过自新 干一份不错的酒保工作
I know you didn't go straight and get an honest job pouring drinks,
告诉我 德罗沙 你在这干什么？
so tell me, DeRosa, what are you doing here?
我也可以问你一样的问题
Could easily ask you the same question.
是啊 当然 这是私人问题
Yeah, well, that's personal.
接到阿比盖尔的电话 这是第一次
Got a call from Abigail, this being the first time
办公室你坐了这么久 又重返战场
you're back in the field after being a desk jockey for so long.
她以为你都快生锈了
She thought you might be a little rusty.
好伤人啊
Oh, that hurts.
他来了
He's here.
- 你也认识那个家伙？- 你是说那个自封的大佬？不认识
- Know that guy as well? - You mean the wannabe gangster? No.
你认出他了？
You recognize him?
要不要给你引荐一下？
Want me to introduce you?
从什么时候开始你和阿比盖尔联系这么紧密？
Since when are you so tight with Abigail?
如你所说 这是私人问题
Like you said, it's personal.
你怎么样 里昂？
How you doing, Leon?
里昂
Leon.
你知道 我的一个手下失踪了
You know, one of my men is missing,
我觉得他是在一座叫哈迪斯的秘密监狱里
and I think he's in a black-site prison called Hades.
有没有想起是哪儿？
Ring a bell anywhere?
还有一家叫做拉什科的公司 欧洲卫星技术公司
And there's this company called Ruscho. European satellite tech company.
他们给你一千万美元 这听起来怎么样？
They gave you about ten million bucks. How about that?
一千万美元
Ten million dollars.
一大笔钱 但我认为这都是胡扯
Lot of money. But I think it's all bullshit.
因为你不是为卫星技术公司当说客
Because you don't lobby for satellite tech.
听着 雷…
Look, Ray...
你是为了利益替秘密监狱当说客 我说的对吗？
You lobby for black-site prison profit, am I right?
- 听着 雷… - 你得告诉我你知道的一切
- Look, Ray... - You're gonna tell me what you know.
快走
Move!
嘿 布雷斯林…
Hey, Breslin...
重操旧业 感觉好吗？
Good to be back?
不 重操旧业实在糟糕
No, it's bad to be back.
- 里昂 你在替谁卖命？- 对不起 雷 我不能…
- Leon, who you working for? - l'm sorry, Ray. I can't...
快走吧 想要份工作吗 德罗沙？
Come on. Want a job, DeRosa?
操 是啊
Fuck,yeah.
有一个私人银行帐户 我需要找人鉴定
There's this private bank account, and I need it identified.
现在他死了 这是我们的唯一线索
With him dead, it's our only lead.
好吧 给我一天时间 我来搞定
All right. Give me a day, I'll figure it out.
嘿
Hey.
你从哪里来的？
Where are you coming from?
我在监狱上班 我是厨师
I work for the prison. I'm the cook.
给我说说厨房
Tell me about the kitchen.
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
从你的囚室怎么能到厨房？
How do I get there from your cell?
我要走了
I got to go.
是的
Yes.
你在动物园里站错了队 我的朋友
You are on the wrong side of the zoo, my friend.
- 我需要你揍我一顿 - 什么？今天是休战日
- I need you to kick my ass. - What? It's a truce day.
再来啊
Come on.
你究竟要干什么？
What the hell are you up to?
以为能说通医生 给我们搞些福利
Thought I could work the doctor, get us some benefits.
结果发现医生是个灯柱子
Turns out the doctor is a lamp stand.
我叫阿卡拉
My name is Akala.
树
Shu.
- 什么？- 他把所有的点联系了起来
- What? - He connected the dots.
你在拉什科的内线送我一个兔子洞
Your inside man at Ruscho sent me down a rabbit hole.
看起来我已经找到了 能带我找到树的人
But it looks like I found a guy who can lead us to Shu.
这个人在哪？
Where is this guy?
现在吗？他在开车我在追
Right now? Driving the car I'm chasing.
相信你知道你在干什么
Sure hope you know what you're doing.
稍后打给你
Call you back.
你躲哪儿去了？
Where you hiding?
该死
Damn it!
他妈的
Fuck me.
囚犯1764号 1765号 请在竞技区报到
Inmates 1764 and 1765, report to the zoo.
重复 在竞技区报到
I repeat, report to the zoo.
他们昨晚又折磨我
They tortured me again last night.
小时候你心理上就比我坚强
You were always mentally tougher than me as a kid.
记得吗？
Remember?
你现在需要坚强
You need to be now.
开始搏斗
Begin battle.
搏斗结束
Battle is over.
囚犯1764号 1765号
Inmates 1764, 1765,
你们赢得了两小时的庇护时光
you've earned two hours of sanctuary time.
负面框架理论
Negative skeleton theory.
利用他们让你所见去绘制不可见
Use what they let you see to map out what you can't see.
这样布局结构才能呈现于你面前
That's how the layout begins to reveal itself to you.
锻炼你的思维 来穿越限制你的实体围墙
Train your mind to look beyond the physical wall that confines you.
囚室另一边是完全不同的世界
There's a whole separate world on the other side of the cells.
走廊 审讯室 医务室 厨房 指挥部
Hallways, interrogation, infirmary, kitchen, HQ.
而现在 全部都是负空间
Right now, it's all negative space.
用不了多久
But not for long.
我会救大家出去
I'm gonna get us out of here.
妈的
Fuck.
快点啊 卢克 你在哪？
Come on, Luke. Where are you?
这是卢克手机上拨出的最后一个号码
This is the last number Luke called on his cell.
日内瓦 拉什科？
Ruscho Geneva?
要我叫哈什进来吗？
Should I get Hush in here?
不用
No.
你知道 有人曾经告诉我…
You know, someone once told me...
破解最难的谜题时
the single most important thing to remember
必须记住的最重要一点是
in solving the hardest riddles
这些谜题是专门设计来骗你的
is that they're designed to trick you.
推翻你自己的假设
Subvert against your own assumptions.
我的假设告诉我 你不可能
And my assumptions are telling me that there's no way
让卢克直接违背公司原则
that you would let Luke go directly against company order.
听着 他只是想出外勤
Look, he just wanted to do the legwork.
这是他独领风潮的良好机会
Thought it was a good chance for him to take the lead on something.
可现在卢克和树都失踪了
And now Luke and Shu are missing.
你是囚犯1924号
You are prisoner 1924.
重复 你是囚犯1924号
I repeat, you are prisoner 1924.
欢迎来到哈迪斯
Welcome to Hades
先生 事情有了眉目 我侵入了他们系统
Sir, I felt something was going on. I hacked into the system,
也就是说 卢克是想去日内瓦找拉什科公司
and basically, Luke tried to meet up with Ruscho Geneva.
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
我告诉他远离那些家伙 他怎么会卷入进去？
I told him to stay away from these guys. How'd he get involved with that?
是我
It was me.
我给了他 我的一个线人的信息
I gave him one of my contacts.
进来吧
Come on.
在你失踪后 布雷斯林开始到处找你
After you went missing, Breslin started digging.
他认为这地方是"坟墓"幕后的同一伙人所建
He thinks this place was started by the same people behind the Tomb,
所以我…
so I...
我搞砸了 最终被困这里
I screwed up. Ended up in here.
没关系 我快搞清布局结构了
Doesn't matter. I'm close to getting the layout.
- 需要我做什么？- 现在不需要
- What do you want me to do? - Nothing yet.
我们越少接触越好
The less contact we have, the better.
树 这不可能是巧合
Shu, it can't be a coincidence
现在布雷斯林的三个专家都被关在这儿
that all three of Breslings specialists are locked up here now.
不 不可能是
No, it can't.
可能他们正在观察我们
Assume they are watching us.
求你了
Please.
他快要把专利交给你们了
He's close to giving it to you.
快要？
Close?
他坚持不了多久
He won't last.
那他就该交出我想要的
Then he needs to give me what I want.
否则我把他喂给其它动物
Or I'll feed him to the rest of the animals.
我小时候就想学做汤饺
I've tried to make soup dumplings since I was a kid,
但每次都是面团和得太硬
but every time, the dough is too stiff.
听着 我不知道你们的交易是什么
Look, I don't know what your deal is,
但是… 我不想死
but... I don't want to die.
他们对你的所做所为都是错的
What they are doing to you is wrong.
让我来帮你回家吧
Then let me help you get home.
从我的囚室去厨房的时候 他们会蒙上我的眼睛
They blindfold me when I go from my cell to the kitchen.
那不是观察事物的唯一途径
That's not the only way to see.
十六 十七 十八 十九 二十
16,17,18,19,20...
多少步？
How many steps?
24步
Twenty-four.
每座监狱送给你的一份礼物就是时间
The one gift every prison gives you is time.
别浪费了这份厚礼
Don't waste it.
利用每次机会设想布局结构
Visualize the layout every chance you have.
今天早上是45步
It was 45 this morning.
什么？
What?
到厨房的步数
Steps to the kitchen.
距离翻倍了？
The distance doubled?
来啊
Come on!
我需要去安全屋
I need to get in the sanctuary.
是吗 我还想要瓶可乐呢
Yeah, and I need a Coke.
好梦
Sweet dreams.
所有囚犯返回各自囚室
All prisoners return to your spoke.
重复 所有囚犯返回各自囚室
I repeat, all prisoners return to your spoke.
即使最复杂的故事通常也都基于一个简单的想法
Even the most complex of narratives are often based on one simple idea.
答案很可能就在你的面前
The answer is most likely right in front of you.
监狱能移动
The prison is moving.
囚室到竞技区的入口会改变
The cell spokes change entry points to the zoo.
像魔方一样？
Like a Rubik's Cube?
我们不了解日常规律 我们不清楚布局结构
We got no routine. We got no layout.
而且我们没有支援
And we have no help.
也许我们有支援
Maybe we do.
新纳粹？
Neo-Nazis?
计算机奇才 他们是前些日子被抓来的
Computer nerds. They brought them in some time back.
他们被集中在冰岛的某个地下室里
They rounded them up in some random basement in Iceland.
他们自称"死亡军团"
They call themselves The Legion.
领袖的名号是"倒计时"
The leader's handle is Count Zero.
他敲诈了"财富"杂志500家公司
He's screwed with more Fortune 500 companies
你我都说不上名字的公司
than you and I can name.
但我们的管理员有个麻烦事
But our zookeeper's got a problem
因为他不知道哪一个是真的"倒计时"
because he doesn't know which one is actually Count Zero.
他日夜审讯
He's interrogated them day and night.
从未赢得过庇护时光
No sanctuary time ever.
监狱为什么要在乎这个？
Why does the prison care?
因为"倒计时"获得了监狱的规格参数
Because Count Zero has acquired the specs to the prison.
他们想知道他是谁 服务器在哪
They need to know who he is and where his servers are.
- 监狱的规格参数？- 是的
- Specs of the prison? - Yes.
如果你能赶在监狱之前找出谁是"倒计时"
If you can find out which one is Count Zero before the prison...
或许他能帮助我们
maybe he can help us.
我要见"臭虫"
I need to see Bug.
我要见… "臭虫"
I need to see... Bug.
如果你想买昆虫之类的书 书在楼上
If you want a book on insects, they're upstairs.
好了 就在这边
Okay. Right this way.
"臭虫"
Bug.
德罗沙？
DeRosa?
麻雀
Sparrow.
- 他是谁？- 别问了 我不会告诉你的
- Who is he? - Come on. I can't give that to you.
昆虫世界
The Insect Society
- 客户永远匿名 - 客户永远匿名
-clients remain anonymous. - Clients remain anonymous.
- 特别是… - 闭嘴 "臭虫"
- Above all else... - Shut up, Bug.
我们哥们一起好多年了
We've been boys for a long time.
我喜欢你们在这里所做的一切
I love what you guys do here.
听着 "臭虫"…
Now, Bug...
如果你还不跟我开口说话
But I'm gonna have to kick the shit out of you
我会打得你屁滚尿流
if you don't start talking to me.
我会告诉你一个名字
I'll get you a name.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还想再要一样东西
I'm gonna need one more thing from you.
雨声快放弃了
Yusheng's close.
时间到了
Time is up.
你在逼他放弃他一生的工作
You're asking him to give up his life's work.
我们大家都知道根本不是这么回事
We both know that that's not what this is about.
你很清楚那项技术能做什么
You know exactly what that tech can do.
时间到了
Time is up!
不
No!
搏斗结束
Battle is over.
囚犯1789号 3486号 6412号
Inmates 1789, 3486, 6412
你们赢得了两小时的庇护时光
you've earned two hours of sanctuary time.
我需要你们的帮助
I need your help.
你们其中一人知道这个地方的布局结构
One of you knows the layout of this place.
等等 安全屋
Wait. The sanctuary.
你们进去过吗？
Have you ever been in?
给我布局结构 我能让你们进去
Give me that layout, I can get you in.
我们是死亡军团
We are Legion.
"倒计时"
Count Zero.
如果你们告诉我布局的逻辑 我就能把大家救出去
If you give me the logic of the layout, I can get us out of here.
(我知道谁是麻雀账号的主人)
(你不会喜欢这个名字的)
(你什么时候给过我喜欢的消息?)
他们是怎么知道的？
How did they know?
金布拉总想要抢你的风头
Kimbral was trying to upstage you.
你告诉了我所有事情
You told me everything.
你是监狱的人
You work for the prison.
我管理着这座监狱
I run the prison.
贾斯珀·金布拉？
Our Jasper Kimbral?
我不明白
I don't get it.
从他离开这儿起 你跟踪他的足迹
You got to follow the footprints from the time he left this place
到他目前所在的位置
to wherever he is now.
哈迪斯肯定在某个地方
Hades has got to be somewhere.
是啊 地下世界
Yeah, the underworld.
阿比盖尔 能让我们单独待一会吗？
Abigail, can you give us a minute?
好的
Okay.
我知道你们之间看法不同 但我愿意听你的想法
I know we've had our differences, but I got to hear it from you.
向我发誓我们之间没有问题
Swear to me we're okay.
你在说什么 伙计？我们之间当然没问题
What are you talking about, man? Of course we're good.
很好
All right.
而且入侵计算机你给的钱也不少 对吧？
And you're still paying me good money to hack shit, right?
我为什么要乱来？
Why would I mess that up?
那么你关起门来都在干些什么？
So what've you been working on behind closed doors?
这样说吧 我正在干一些
Let's just say I'm working on something
能够改善我们之间沟通的事
that will improve the communications between us.
你好啊 树
Hello, Shu.
你已经见过我们的动物园管理员了
You've met my Zookeeper.
我们无法击破他们
We couldn't break 'em.
真是了不起
Extraordinary.
三个人 都不愿意互相背叛
Three men, and they wouldn't turn on one another.
可是你…
But you...
你让他们站在你这一边
you've got them on your side.
你让他们都相信你
You got them to trust you.
我期待了很长时间想在你脸上看到那种表情
I've waited a long time to see that look on your face.
看看谁在这里 是卢克
Look who's here. It's Lukey.
快说说 难道你们俩相互见面不开心吗？
Aw, come on. Aren't you guys happy to see each other?
当这个地方的投资人发现雷·布雷斯林的门徒们
When the investors of this place found out that Ray Breslings protege
被解除了关系 你们可以想象
had been cut loose, you can imagine.
布雷斯林让他们的最近一次投资损失了大把银子
Breslin cost them a lot of money on their last investment.
这些人不喜欢血本无归
These people do not like losing money.
他们需要一个更好的…
They needed someone better...
更现代的
more current,
所以… 瞧
so... voila.
欢迎来到哈迪斯
Welcome to Hades.
所以 你是为了复仇才把我们关在这里
So, we're here because you want your revenge.
是的
Yes.
坚定 彻底 明确
Unwavering, complete and definitive.
明白了吧 动物园里的每个人对我来说都是财富
See, everyone in this zoo is worth money to me.
他们拥有的信息总能让外面的人
They all have information that someone out there
开出百万美元的价格…
thinks is worth millions of dollars...
特别是你的表弟雨声
especially your cousin Yusheng.
你们俩…
You two...
你们对我一文不值
you're worth nothing to me.
那为什么不杀了我们做个了断？
Then why don't you kill us and get it over with?
你的战斗精神在哪 卢克？
Where's your fighting spirit at, Luke? Huh?
设计这种地方就是给你希望
This place is designed to give you hope.
赢得搏斗 你就获得福利
You win a battle, you get benefits.
读读书 作作画
Read a book. Make art.
搏斗失败 你就饿肚子
You lose a battle, then you lose food.
开始怀疑自己
Start to doubt yourself.
然后你确立目标 死而复生
Then you set goals, and you rise again.
人类本性的所有戏剧性都在这里有所体现
All the drama of the human condition is represented right here
就体现在我的动物园里
in my zoo.
我要保证你们俩忙个不停
I'm gonna make sure that you two have plenty to do.
等你们醒过来的时候 你们就成了出卖"倒计时"的人
When you wake up, you'll be the men who sold out Count Zero.
那能给你一种了解人类本性的独特视觉
That should give you a unique perspective on the human condition.
囚犯1764号 在竞技区参加搏斗
Inmate 1764, report for battle in the zoo.
囚犯1924号 在竞技区参加搏斗
Inmate 1924, report for battle in the zoo.
搏斗开始
Begin battle.
他在这里一天 就要确保他每天参加搏斗
When he's in the zoo, make sure he fights every day.
树不再有休战日了…
There are no more truce days for Shu...
直到他的意志被摧毁 让我们拿到雨声的技术
until his will is broken and we have Yusheng's technology.
所以你没有布局结构 没有日常规律
So you have no layout. There is no routine.
也没有支援
And you have no help.
但凡事必有备用计划 即使是对付这些混蛋
But there's always a plan B, even for these assholes.
他们想方设法使这个地方看上去完全自动化
They try to make this place look totally automated,
但我们还是能看到人类警卫
but you saw those human guards.
那就是他们的备用计划
That's their plan B.
你的呢 树？
What is yours, Shu?
他们还活着
They're alive.
金布拉 进展汇报
Kimbral, report.
我们比以前更接近摧毁雨声
We're closer than ever to breaking Yusheng.
接近？
Closer?
好吧 等你摧毁的时候再汇报
Well, report back when you do.
集中更多精力获取专利而不是复仇
Focus more on getting that patent than your revenge.
带他来这里就是冒险
It's a risk bringing him here.
他能打过那些机器
He beat their last facility.
我要给他们看看 他打不过我
I'm gonna show them he can't beat mine.
举起手来
Let's see some hands!
让我们看清你的双手
Now! Let's see 'em!
目标已投降
Target's compliant.
- 我们抓到了他 - 带他进来
- Yeah, we got him. - Bringing him in now.
把他锁起来 把他…
Lock him up, lock him...
在此之前一切只存在于理论中
Before it was all theoretical.
什么样的设计是最好的
What design is best,
什么样的策略能对付什么样的防御
what strategy works against what defense.
现在这都能得以实现
But now it's real.
你对抗我
You against me.
好吧 你赢了
All right, you won.
还没有
Not yet.
我曾尝试更多的算法 好让机器负责管理行动
I wanted to go more algorithms, let the machines run the show.
你说不行
You said no.
你大谈人类的直觉 团队合作的价值
You talked about human intuition. The value of teamwork.
既然你们三个都在这里
Well, there's three of you now.
演示给我看
Show me.
所有囚犯在竞技区报到
All prisoners report to the zoo.
重复 所有囚犯在竞技区报到
I repeat, all prisoners report to the zoo.
囚犯9051号 在竞技区参加搏斗
Inmate 9051, report for battle in the zoo.
重复 在竞技区参加搏斗
I repeat, report for battle in the zoo.
搏斗开始
Begin battle.
搏斗结束 重复 搏斗结束
Battle is over. I repeat, battle is over.
你有一条新的消息
You have one new message.
德罗沙 我是哈什 他们抓走了布雷斯林
DeRosa, it's Hush. They took Breslin.
我们所有人都在哈迪斯
All our guys are in Hades.
你是唯一能帮助我们脱逃的人
You're the only one that can help us get 'em out.
给我回电
Call me.
树… 你不能放弃
Shu... you can't give up.
你对放弃又了解多少？
What would you know about giving up?
你从来没有坚持过什么
You never stood for anything.
树 对不起
Shu, I'm sorry.
你只是想赚钱
You just wanted to be rich.
那有什么错？
What's wrong with that?
我家总是没有钱
My family never had any money.
你父母去世后 我们还要替你还债
And when your parents died, we had to pay for you, too.
好吧？你可千万别忘了那些
Okay? Don't you ever forget that.
继续 继续
Go ahead. Go ahead!
打我啊 快啊
Lash out! Do it!
当你无法控制自己的时候 你就是这个样子
It's what you've always done when you can't control things.
你一直是老样子
You're always the same.
怎么了？
What?
你说的对
You are right.
我总是能让人猜透
I'm predictable.
金布拉知道我们要做什么
Kimbral knew what we were gonna do.
他在玩弄我的自负
He played to my arrogance.
他知道我会不顾一切救大家出去
He knew I'd take it upon myself to get us out.
他把我们玩弄于股掌之中
He played us perfectly.
我们怎么才能反击他？
How do we play him?
备用计划
Plan B.
我们要让他没法猜透
We stop being so predictable.
我准备开口了
I'm ready to talk.
技术细节很复杂
The tech details are complex.
我会按步骤告诉你们细节
I will give them to you in stages.
告诉我所有细节 否则免谈
Give me everything,
- 我们连上了 - 雷 你能听到我吗？
- We're in. - Ray, you hear me?
- 我听得很清楚 - 太好了
- I can hear you clearly. - Yes!
谁能想到你的业余牙医技术还能起作用？
Who knew your amateur dentist skills would pay off?
现在你们满意我上班时间待在游戏室了吧？
Now aren't you glad I spent all of those company hours in my playroom?
- 有什么消息？- 我连续熬夜三个晚上
- What do you got? - I been up for three nights straight.
密码破解器挖到宝了
Password breaker hit the motherlode.
我已经突破了防火墙进入了伽利略主机
I'm through the firewall and into the Galileo mainframe.
正在接收哈迪斯所有系统的数据
Receiving good reads from all systems at Hades.
我最好的定位系统蜘蛛正在超时工作
My best GPS spiders are working overtime,
我们现在只得到33%的布局结构
and we only have 33% of the layout.
没有适合你们的撤退方案
No exact exit strategy for you.
我们需要内部的一个接入点
We need an access point from the inside.
你需要去找雨声帮忙
You need to get Yusheng to work on it.
我们被全天侯监控
We got eyes on us 24/7.
- 你能干掉摄像头吗？- 可以
- Can you get the cameras? - Yeah.
- 我只能保证一分钟 - 70秒
- I can guarantee a minute. - Seventy seconds.
或许70秒 但在那之后 他们就知道了
Maybe 70 seconds, but after that, it's gonna know.
我没问题
I'll take it.
还有一件事需要你去做
There's one more thing I want you to do.
你能控制伽利略的语音盒子吗？
Can you get access to Galileo's voice box?
我们是个集体 要动大伙一块动
Let's move together. Flow as one.
那个音箱出什么问题了？
What's wrong with the boom box?
我们是个集体 要动大伙一块动
Let's move together. Flow as one.
那是青岛话
That's Qingdao
48号到58号摄像头覆盖B区
Cameras 48 through 58 cover spoke B.
我们用30秒就能清除摄像头
We can clear it in 30 seconds.
开始
Now.
68秒
Sixty-eight.
66秒
Sixty-six.
你到头来还是学会了我的语言
You managed to learn my language after all.
我们只有70秒时间
We only got about 70 seconds.
哈什正在获取关键数据
Hush is trying to get the critical data,
但到目前为止他只拿到了33%的布局结构
but he's only got 33% of the layout so far.
没有发现到出口的直接路径
No direct paths to the exits.
他侵入了伽利略？
He's hacking Galileo?
- 是的 他需要我们支援 - 不到40秒了
- Affirmative. He's gonna need our help. - Less than 40 seconds.
这是一种倒像设计
This is an inverted design
可以保护中心区域和控制室不受外界的破坏
that protects the center and control rooms from the outside in,
因此才很难从外面攻破
that's what makes it so difficult.
我们必须从内部给他一个物理接入点
We need to give him a physical access point from the inside.
告诉雨声 让他搞定这个
Talk to Yusheng. Get him to work on it.
只有10秒了
Ten seconds. Now.
有点耐心
Just be patient.
我听说在铁路附近的仓库里还有飞车追逐
I heard that a car chase went down at the warehouse complex near the rail yard.
其中一辆车是卢克的
One of the cars was Luke's.
过去检查一下
Going down there to check it out.
我会搞定的
I'll figure it out.
好啦 布雷斯林和同伴正从里面想办法
All right. Breslin and the guys are working from the inside
借助仪器帮助我们定位哈迪斯
on a device that will help us locate Hades.
很好
Great.
你找到这些人 我要进去了
You find these guys, I want in
我们再联络
I'll be in touch.
囚室里我们能相信的人都参加
The guys we can trust in most of the spokes are in.
一切就绪
Be ready.
管理员拿到了参数 不管他把这些参数给谁
The Zookeeper has the specs. Only a matter of time
他们很快会发现参数无效 这只是时间问题
before whoever he's giving them to realizes they won't work.
你从没想过学围棋吧
You have never wanted to learn Go.
我建议你学学
I'd recommend it.
围棋里最重要的内容就是耐心
Patience is the most important part of this game.
听到我说的话了吗？我们得走了
Did you hear what I just said? We got to go.
我们有人手 但没有出路
We have the manpower, but no way out.
我们正在寻找
We keep working.
不过首先 我们需要你的帮助
But first, we need your help.
我知道你能帮囚犯搞到东西
I know you get stuff for inmates.
我需要你帮忙 否则我就告诉机器人
I need a favor, or I tell the machine.
我们是个集体
You move all the pieces together.
大伙一块行动
Everything flows as one.
建立了和内部接入点的联系
Connection with inside access point established.
哈迪斯已定位 正在扫描布局结构
Hades located. Scanning layout now.
我们有了布局结构 也清楚了他们的日常规律
We have the layout. We know their routine.
支援怎么办？
What about help?
我们也有支援
We got that covered.
- 我准备关闭伽利略系统 - 好
- I'm ready to shut Galileo down. - Okay.
我们的撤退方案非常可靠
Our exit strategy is solid,
但要通过那些人类警卫还得靠运气
but you still got to get lucky to get past those human guards.
竞技区的每一边都有两扇门
There's two maintenance doors on either side of the zoo.
灯光熄灭后 你们有三分钟时间
When the lights go out, you got three minutes
然后系统会重新启动
before the system starts waking up again.
演出开始了
Showtime.
系统遭受攻击
System under attack.
系统连接失败
System failure.
所有系统关闭
All systems down.
时间紧迫 门重新锁上前 我们得用用我们的肌肉了
Clock's ticking. Time to use those muscles before the doors relock.
- 好了 来吧 推 - 推
- All right, come on. Push. - Push.
我是伽利略 所有系统重新上线
I am Galileo. All systems online.
停下
Halt!
入侵者正穿过23号大厅往西逃去
The intruders are heading west through hall 23.
这边可以到医疗中心
This way to the medical center.
德罗沙 你的预感是对的 哈迪斯的位置已确定
DeRosa, your hunch was right. Location of Hades confirmed.
正在给你发坐标
Sending you the coordinates now.
建立通信联系
Communication established
雷·布雷斯林打算破坏哈迪斯
Ray Breslin is attempting to break Hades.
我要让你见识一下监狱有什么能耐
I want you to see how the prison responds.
医疗机器人仍处于离线状态
The med bots are still down.
系统未能全部上线
The system isn't fully online.
我需要你们几个怪人掩护我们
I need you cue balls to cover our back.
我们是死亡军团
We are Legion.
无所谓了 我们走 快点
Whatever. Let's go. Come on!
掩护他们
Cover their asses.
所有通讯受阻 闭路系统已激活
All communications blocked. Closed-circuit system activated.
金布拉切断了通讯
Kimbral cut communications.
他屏蔽了我们 切断了通讯链路
He shut us down. Closed off the com link.
我们的机器人怎么样？
What about our bots?
仍然正常 但已经最小化了
They're still working but minimized.
他关闭了伽利略的核心功能
He's walled off Galileo's prime function.
信道有干扰 我无法控制它
Without a clear channel, I can't control it.
入侵者在37号走廊
The intruders are on corridor 37.
关闭进入主楼层的所有通道
Clearing all access to main floor.
重新设置哈迪斯结构至安全状态
Resetting Hades structure to secure position.
妈的 现在怎么办？
Shit. What do we do?
哈迪斯重设结构完成
Hades restructure complete.
伽利略…
Galileo...
释放瓦斯
gas them.
布雷斯林 德克勒克
Breslin, Declerc.
重叠在一起的两层圆形地板 像生日蛋糕
Two circular floors on top of each other like a birthday cake.
通风系统
The ventilation system.
两套空气调节系统 连接通风孔和天花板
Two HVACs, flow vents and ceiling.
在上面
UP there!
雨声 快点
Yusheng. Come on.
找到你了
There you are.
我们从医疗中心后退
We're getting pushback from the terminal in medical.
我们马上就有同伴了
We're about to have company.
朝哪边走？
Anyone got a coin?
你怎么破解迷宫？
How do you beat a maze?
靠右行走
Stick to the right.
站住 不许动 否则我们开火了
Freeze! Freeze, or we'll open fire!
快关门
Seal us up!
不知道我们还能坚持多久
Don't know how long we can hold it.
继续走
Keep going!
我要回去找卢克
I'm going back for Luke.
好的 我去控制室
All right. I'm going to the control room.
雨声 跟我一起来
Yusheng, come with me.
- 不许动 - 举起手来
- Freeze! - Show me your hands!
- 举起手来 - 别动 不许动
- Show me your hands! - Hold it! Don't move!
- 我们是死亡军团 - 我们是死亡军团
- We are Legion. - We are Legion.
我们必须同步 数到一 三 二 一
We got to be in sync. On one. Three, two, one.
- 好了 你知道该做什么 - 是的 走
- All right, you know what to do. - Yes. Go.
医疗中心安全
Medical secured.
金布拉 汇报进展
Kimbral, report.
他是很棒
He's good,
但是我的机器总能获胜
but my machine always wins.
那可不一定
Not sure about that.
好吧
Okay.
我投降 你抓到我了
I give up. You got me.
但是你们还是在哈迪斯里面
But you're still in Hades.
一旦伽利略恢复到全功率 我只要触发自动命令
And with Galileo back to his full power, I just triggered his autopilot orders.
哈什正在攻击的所有系统都会关闭
All the systems that Hush was attacking are now closed.
你们将永远走不出这里
You're never getting out of here.
知道吧 孩子 我要给你奖励分
You know, kid, I got to give you credit.
你在这里完成了一项伟大的工作
You did a great job here.
你建造了一个监狱 看起来似乎…
You built a prison. Looks like it has...
没有弱点
no weaknesses.
但是你知道吗？
But you know what?
凡事总有弱点
There is always one.
不错
Oh, yeah.
现在我是管理员
Now I am the Zookeeper.
我有一位熟人朋友
I have this acquaintance friend of mine.
大个子 他帮了我一个忙
Big guy. And he did me a favor.
我给了他这个帐户 特别的帐户
I gave him this account number, special.
我破解不了密码 但他可以
Couldn't crack the code, but he did.
他追踪到了这笔钱 随之追踪到了帐户
And he traced the money, and he traced the account.
麻雀
Sparrow.
你就是隐藏在幕后的人
And you're the one who's behind all this.
我们制定了计划
Then we made a plan.
太阳能系统错误 太阳能系统温度升高
Solar system failure. Solar system heating up.
我刚告诉过你伽利略马上会恢复全功率
I just told you Galileo was back to his full power.
根本不需要太阳能
It doesn't need solar.
让它爆炸吧
Let it blow.
发现出口 德罗沙 正如说好的
There's the opening, DeRosa, as promised.
雨声
Yusheng.
- 不许动 - 趴下
- Freeze! - Get down!
不许动
Freeze!
我本来要花很长时间才能找到这个地方
I could've been looking for this place for a long time.
我会找到的
I would've found it,
但从外面突破要困难得多
but it's a lot tougher breaking in from the outside.
其实我知道不必那样 因为我了解你
But I knew that wasn't gonna happen because I know you.
我知道你是怎么想的…
I know how you think...
我也知道你会来找我 你也确实来了
and I knew you would be coming for me, and you did.
我很高兴 因为我喜欢这种工作
I'm glad, because I like working,
如你所见 从里往外攻破
as you can see, from the inside out.
哈迪斯有一个特别 特别 特别软弱的地方
Hades had one very, very, very weak spot.
就是你
You.
主门安全漏洞 强行进入
Security breach at main door. Forced entry.
哈迪斯和解
Hades compromised.
到时间了 我们就此结束吧
It's time. Let's finish it right.
停下来 停下来 趴下
Stop! Stop! Get on the ground!
马上趴下 我们走
On the ground now! Let's go!
趴下 趴到地上
Down! Down on the ground!
德罗沙 好久没见了
DeRosa, long time no see.
外套不错 你的泰迪熊在哪？
Nice PJs. Where's your fucking teddy bear?
囚犯9051号 在竞技区参加搏斗
Prisoner 9051, report for battle in the zoo.
我们倒要看看没了那些高科技 你有什么本事
Let's see what you can do without your tech.
等我的拳头落在你的脸上 我会折磨死你 孩子
After I put my fist through your face, I'm gonna crucify you, kid.
我错过了什么？
What'd I miss?
这下我们扯平了
Guess that makes us even.
谢谢 卢克
Thanks,Luke.
嗯
Yeah.
嘿
Hey!
- 放松 - 他终于来了
- Relax. - There he is.
很高兴你加入我们
Nice of you to join us.
过了一段自由时光
Had some free time.
上车 上车 快上车
Get in, get in, get in!
哈什 能听到我吗？
Hush, you hear me?
听到你的声音太好了 我们以为失去你了
Good to hear you. We thought we lost you.
树和雨声安然无恙
Shu and Yusheng are safe and sound.
结果怎么样？
How about that?
备用计划成功
Plan B actually worked.
记住 树 智力加上耐心 一切皆有可能
Remember, Shu, with brains and patience, nothing's impossible.
有没有人告诉我我们究竟在哪儿？
Can somebody tell me where the hell we are?
你要告诉他吗 大个子？
You want to tell him, big guy?
并不想
Not really.
亚特兰大
Atlanta.
你他妈不是逗我玩吧？
Are you fucking kidding me?
哈迪斯在亚特兰大？怎么可能？
Hades is in Atlanta? How is that possible?
金布拉 汇报进展
Kimbral, come in. Report.
你不是金布拉
You're not Kimbral.
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
我要告诉你一件事 我真的非常讨厌这堆狗屎
But I got to tell you something. I'm really getting sick of this shit.
所以不管你是谁…
So whoever you are...
不管你在哪…
wherever you are...
我们都会找到你…
we're gonna find you...
毫无疑问
for sure.
《金蝉脱壳2：冥府》